Viewers all over the world,
begin to reason with yourself right now.
Reason with yourself -
you will see what Satan might have used
You will see what satan is using
to connect you to himself.
He wants you to be unhappy,
he wants you to be sad.
He wants you to look at Jesus in a bad light.
Reason with your self you will see what Satan is using
to connect you to himself.
It can be sickness, infirmity, stagnation,
nightmares, loneliness or depression.
These are the tools of satan.
Whatever satan might have been
using to connect you to himself,
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen by faith in Jesus Name.
be broken in the name of Jesus!
You want to be happy, but when
this pain, affliction and whatever
challenging situation comes, it changes your joy.
Be broken in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen by faith in Jesus Name.
When Jesus says Yes, no one can say No.
I can hear chains falling!
Chains of setback - I can hear chains falling!
Chains of stagnation - I can hear chains falling!
Chains of failure - I can hear chains falling!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen by faith in Jesus Name.
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen by faith in Jesus Name.
Rejoice!
TT: Lizz ndungu
Date: 27/10/2018